<terms>
<preface>
<content>
Please take a moment to read these terms and conditions including our terms to understand how they apply to your use of our website and any products or services that you may access.
</content>
<content>
If you have any questions regarding our website, the Terms, products or services, please to contact us at +248 4225574
</content>
</preface>
<term>
<title>Website details</title>
<content>
The Central Point Pharmacy website at www.website.com is owned and operated by Central Point Pharmacy, a company registered in the Seychelles, under company registration number xxxx/xxxxxx/xx, which has its head office at PO Box 1448, Le-Chantier Mall, Francis-Rachel Street, Victoria, Mahe.
</content>
</term>
<term>
<title>Terms and conditions apply</title>
<content>
These Terms apply to your use of this website. By using this website, you acknowledge that you have read and understood these Terms and agree to be bound by them. They represent our entire agreement with you and supersede all prior terms, conditions, warranties and/or representations to the extent permitted by law. Please do not use our website if you do not agree to be bound by these Terms.
</content>
</term>
<term>
<title>Change in terms</title>
<content>
We may periodically update or change the Terms of this website without giving you prior notice. You should check them regularly, as your continued use of our website means that you accept any updated or revised Terms.
</content>
</term>
<term>
<title>Applicable law</title>
<content>
This agreement is governed by the laws of pharmacy act of Seychelles.
</content>
</term>
<term>
<title>Use of our website</title>
<content>
You are welcome to browse or use our website for your own personal and non-commercial information purposes only. No other use is permitted without our prior written consent. The unauthorised use, copying, reproduction, variation, modification or distribution of the content of this website, the uploading of any unlawful or damaging information or viral software, or the creation of any links to our website from any other site whatsoever, is strictly prohibited.
</content>
<content>
You agree to indemnify us against any loss, damage, harm, claim or any other cost whatsoever that we may sustain as a result of your use of our website and/or its contents contrary to these Terms.
</content>
<content>
We reserve the rights to take legal action by the law of Seychelles, in our sole discretion, determine that you are not using the website in compliance with these Terms or if we believe the information provided by you is untrue, inaccurate or incomplete.
Any indulgence of extension of time granted to you shall not be construed as a waiver or variation of any of our rights or remedies in these Terms or law.
</content>
</term>
<term>
<title>Privacy policy &amp; Information Security</title>
<content>
Your privacy is very important to us and therefore any information that you upload on our website will be stored on a secure server. We will not disclose, sell or rent your personal information to third parties without your consent unless we are compelled to do so by law.
</content>
<content>
Whilst all reasonable efforts are taken to ensure that your personal information are protected as they travel over the internet, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information you exchange with us.
You may visit the website without providing any personal information.  The website servers will in such instances collect the IP address of your computer, but not the email address or any other distinguishing information.  This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent at the website, pages viewed, etc.  Central Point Pharmacy uses this information to determine the use of the website, and to improve the content thereon.
</content>
</term>
<term>
<title>Accuracy of website contents</title>
<content>
All reasonable steps are taken to ensure that the information on our website, social media channels and email marketing is accurate and up-to-date. We do not, however, warrant that the content or information displayed is always accurate, complete and/or current. Errors and omissions excepted(E&amp;OE).
</content>
</term>
<term>
<title>Intellectual Property</title>
<content>
All rights, including copyright, trade mark and other intellectual property rights embodied in any logos, text, images, video, audio or other material on this website are owned by or licensed to us. All data and information communicated to or from the website including its database also belongs solely to us or our licensors. You agree to sign all documents as we may reasonably require in order to assign any rights that you may acquire in the content of our website. You agree also to waive any moral rights in such content. You are permitted to view, print or store electronically a copy of any information on our website, including these Terms, solely for your personal, lawful, non-commercial use. Unauthorised use, reproduction, modification and/or distribution is strictly prohibited and constitutes an unlawful infringement of our intellectual property rights.
</content>
</term>
<term>
<title>Use of our logos, content and images</title>
<content>
You are not permitted to use the content of our website, our logos or any other images that appear on our website without our prior written consent. Unauthorised use, reproduction, modification and/or distribution is strictly prohibited and constitutes an infringement of our or our licensors’ intellectual property rights.
Advertising
</content>
</term>
<term>
<title>Disclaimers and Exclusions of Liability</title>
<content>
Use of our website is entirely at your own risk. We make no representations or warranties of any kind, whether express or implied. We do not warrant that the functions provided by the website will be uninterrupted or error free, or that the website or the server that makes it available are free from viruses or other harmful components. We accept no liability, to the extent permitted by law, for any direct, indirect, incidental, special or consequential loss or damage of any kind whatsoever or howsoever caused arising from the access or use of our website or the purchase of any of our products or services through our website.
</content>
<content>
You agree, to the extent permitted by law, to indemnify us against any loss or damage suffered or liability incurred by reason of any act or omission on your part or that of any third party acting on your behalf in connection with your use of our website and/or your purchase of any products or services from our website.
</content>
<content>
In the event that any clause contained in these Terms is invalid or unenforceable, then such clause shall not affect the validity or enforceability insofar as the remaining clauses of these Terms are concerned.
</content>
<content>
We shall not be regarded as having waived, or be precluded from exercising any right under these Terms by reason merely that we have provided any indulgence to you or we fail to exercise or delay exercising any right we may have, whether the same right or any other right.
</content>
</term>
</terms>