<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<about>
<introduction>
<icon>introduction.png</icon>
<title>Introduction</title>
<content>
Medsilo pharmaceuticals was started with a mission to thrive in pharmaceutical trade. Our precedence is to deal out reasonable and world class medication with reasonable fee to aid people better.
</content>
<content>
We hope that our products will sustain people to feel healthier and live longer. Our drug range across therapeutic ranges such as  Antibiotics, Analgesic&#47;Anti-Inflammatory, G.I.T, Anti-Allergics&#47;Anti-cough, Antihelmintics, and Nutritional&#47;Supplements. We venture to touch the lives of our clients by devotedly heeding and retorting to their needs with break through vital to their management of ailment.
</content>
<content>
We at Medsilo  venture to deliver access to effective and allied health care services to the public who want them. Medsilo knows the essential status of patient focused health care and guaranteeing the patient requirements are the focus of healthcare policy discussions, regardless of therapeutic area or precise geography. We will carry on our staunch efforts to become a firm that can meet the diagnosis of our patients and to win strong trust among them. We expect to have your implacable support.
</content>
</introduction>
<vision>
<icon>vision.png</icon>
<title>Vision</title>
<content>
We guard the safety, retreat and reliability of the drug distribution system through the keen role of structured pharmacy technicians. 
</content>
<content>
Distinguishing that the pharmacy staff is our key reserve employing and holding very skilled pharmacists and supportive personnel. Instructing patients on the safe use of medications. Providing health training programs to the community to avert disease and support public health. 
</content>
<content>
To be acknowledged nation wide and globally as a front runner in pharmacy business that sanction the apt use of medicine for the well being and security of the community.
</content>
</vision>
<mission>
<icon>mission.png</icon>
<title>Mission</title>
<content>
Our mission to improve the class of life by  permitting  people to do more, feel healthier and live longer. This task drives us to make a genuine difference to the lives of public with true health care solutions. We are refining people&#39;s class of life by preventing, appeasing or curing ailment.
</content>
</mission>
<marketing>
<icon>marketing.png</icon>
<title>Marketing</title>
<content>
We have a marketing division, which takes care of our business across India. We regularly get the opinion of Doctors and patient and try to utilize it for the enhanced services for the public. We recurrently carry out medical camps.
</content>
</marketing>
</about>