<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<features>
<para_1>
<icon>progressive.png</icon>
<title>Progessive</title>
<content>
Medsilo Pharmaceuticals Pvt Ltd is incessantly progressing under the proficient leadership of our managing experts. We are affianced in manufacturing and supply an extensive range of formulations such as tablets, injections and new drugs that are DCGI Approved. These comprise of Antibiotic &amp; Anti-Infectives, Anticold &amp; Anti Allergics. Apart from these, our ranges also include Gastro &amp; Antiemetic &amp; Anti Ulcerant, and Nutritional Supplements. Our whole range also encompasses Tablets, Oral Liquid, Capsules, Injectables, Ointment and Eye &amp; Ear Drops.
</content>
</para_1>
<para_2>
<icon>infrastructure.png</icon>
<title>Infrastructure</title>
<content>
We have a well developed infrastructure as well as panel of skilled and experienced professionals to meet the mass requirements of our client. We have GMP &amp; WHO certification for Tablet, Syrup and Capsule. We pack our products in newest Alu Alu packing. In Medsilo Pharmaceuticals all production is carried in GMP certified units. Our company provides Visual Aids, Reminder Cards as part of marketing strategy. Our company keeps all Franchise and Business Associates well informed about product details and new launches. Order Execution within 24 hours.
</content>
</para_2>
<para_3>
<icon>branded.png</icon>
<title>Branded</title>
<content>
Medsilo Pharmaceuticals is committed to deliver exclusive branded healthcare products which have a constructive impact on consumer&#39;s quality of life. Medsilo Pharmaceuticals specialise in sales, marketing and distribution for licensed healthcare medicines and medical devices. The sales and marketing team is expert in their field and have knowledge in launching new products in market, enhancing brand identity. Medsilo Pharmaceuticals has a proven track record of profitably marketing products to healthcare professionals resulting in their products being accessible on prescription. We are able to create tailored solutions for individual needs from sales and brand development to pick and pack facilities and storeroom and logistics.
</content>
</para_3>
<para_4>
<icon>manufacturing.png</icon>
<title>Manufacturing</title>
<content>
We are offering contract manufacturing for Domestics and Export Market with the manufacturing facility at excise free zone of Baddi, Himachal Pradesh. Time is money for us. As all contract manufacturers insist that their commodities are delivered within contractual time frames. The success of a Contract manufacturer mainly depends on whether it is competent of meeting this prerequisite of Customers. Maintaining a reliable and firm delivery schedule involves secure planning of the whole production.
</content>
</para_4>
<para_5>
<icon>exporting.png</icon>
<title>Exporting</title>
<content>
We began our exports with a wide range of specific products that were branded across segments and dosage forms. Finally, within a couple of years, exports rose and soon accounted for 50% of the entire turnover of the organization.
</content>
</para_5>
</features>