<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faqs>
<faq>
<question>
How to place an order ?
</question>
<answer>
To place an order using our website, go to any of our products section from our website menu at the top, for example Women - Sling Handbags. Once you are in the product section page, choose the products you want to place for order by adding quantity and click Add to Cart button. Then click the cart icon on menu at top. Now verify your cart and checkout. In the checkout page, fill in your appropriate contact details and click Place Order button to complete your order process. 
</answer>
</faq>
<faq>
<question>
What kind of payment for the order is accepted ?
</question>
<answer>
Right now, we accept only Cash on Delivery payment method. Once you have placed your order, you will be provided with your purchase order details, as well as we will receive the same details. Once we have processed your order request, we will contact you for confirmation and on receiving your order package, you will be asked to pay cash for the order and you will receive an order bill for the same at your door step. 
</answer>
</faq>
<faq>
<question>
How soon will I get my ordered products ?
</question>
<answer>
Lumibella fashion guarantee its customers with a time period of 5 days from the day of order placed to deliver the ordered products to its customers. In case of locations far away or location not coming under our service reach limits will take few more days than the guaranteed delivery time.
</answer>
</faq>
<faq>
<question>
How to check stock availability ?
</question>
<answer>
For more ease, our website provides you a stock validator along with other product quantity related validations. You will be notified with a status message as soon as you click the Add to Cart button in the products section page. If the quantity of the product you entered is more than the quantity in our stock for that product, you will be notified with a &#39;Quantity limit exceeded&#39; message below the Add to cart button. You can also check the product stock availabilty on your My Cart page. 
</answer>
</faq>
<faq>
<question>
How to contact Lumibella fashions ?
</question>
<answer>
Visit our Contact Us page from the menu at the top to get more details about our location and contact information. 
</answer>
</faq>
</faqs>